Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Venno's true might had awoken within him, and with it, staggeringly massive power.
Asta called on all of his remaining strength to face the beast.
The way I see it, not giving up is the strongest weapon I've got!
And there's no way I'm gonna quit before my wish comes true, do you understand me? Not ever!
Asta's courage spurred his teammates into action.
I'm here now solely because of your refusal to give up the fight.
Our juniors are giving it all they've got. Time for us to show off our most advanced stuff!
We're not about to let you die, Asta. We'll be fighting beside you.
Let's do this!
Nice try, Grass.
But the spatial spell's power in your aura give away your every move!
Move!
What?
The Thread's trajectory shifted.
This is my weapon!
Now watch! I will defeat you!
We'll be dating soon!
From far away,
bis ashame
Wish us a path
closed away
Here we go
We have a chance to reagan
I understood
Let's get up
chalk
Wow
運命の凍らに I'm falling down
君と奏いたハーモニーまで過去に置き去りのまま
君の強気の範囲はまだ心に引きつったまま
待ただけじゃもう足りない
Just move it next
Wow!
Can't fool it back!
ivid shines on love
Ignition of prince!
Can't fool it back!
Back up action of element
La la la la la la
Can't fool it back!
La la la la la
Nodoma enokimu uchukamate
Now keep it up
I don't know what you're talking about
I didn't do anything
That was all you and Finral
Amazing
Who knew that those two had that kind of talent in them
As I suspected
I can't heal this
Did he cut off the very flow of my self-healing magic?
That's the only weapon here that stands a chance of defeating me
His anti-magic sword
Even with it that runt would be no match for me on his own
But with those two giving him back up he has considerably more mobility
The spatial magic is troublesome
But the real nuisance here is that woman's thread magic
There are threads strung all through this space
They could come into play at any time from any corner
The threads themselves lack the strength to attack or bind me on their own
But they're too fine for the eye to see or for their magic power to be felt
Which means I can't predict the brat's moves
How fascinating
Taken separately you humans are so much trash
But with three of you working together it seems you can actually fight
And I find that disgusting
You may think there's strength in numbers
But that's just an illusion
You have no hope
He's coming
Get ready
All right
Go, Finral
Yeah
I'm not done
All right
It's gonna take a lot more than that
We could cover him in scratches and it wouldn't be enough to take him down
We think we're about to get even more dangerous here
We have to get the kid in as close as we possibly can
Give me right up in his furry face
I'll give it everything I've got
So I'm not imagining things
But now
It feels like an immense and malevolent power
Whatever it is, it's even more unbelievably massive than the unbelievably massive magic I felt earlier
It's unbelievably unbelievable
Shut up!
Quit babbling like an idiot!
Please don't look at me!
Get over it already
We need to do something
Has your magic recovered at all?
Um
No
Not even a little
Sorry
I used up all of mine against that chain magic loser
I couldn't manage a single reflector ray right now
This is just great
Hey little piggy
Don't tell me you went on alone
Seriously?
Are you already stuffing your face again?
Using that freck of the sleeping sheep spell
Empty my tummy along with all of my magic reserves
You wouldn't expect me to fight on an empty stomach, would you?
Come on
We might as well fill our flowers while we wait for our magic to recover!
Yeah, I guess you're right
Eating a little can't hurt
We'll find the others once we're rested
Um, okay
Uh
The magic knights are unstoppable!
They're up against a real monster!
Do you think they actually beat him?
Yes, that's it!
That's the spirit!
Go get him!
The best defense is a good offense!
Keep going and don't give him a chance to fight back!
When I think of what that monster did to my son and my grandkids!
Avenge them!
Give him back every ounce of pain that he gave them!
Well done
Make him suffer!
Those two are normally useless!
But by joining forces they've pushed past their limits!
Still
Not again!
He took another blow!
Is this what I think?
I can't lose focus for a single second!
I'm not sure how much longer I can stand this kind of tension!
So close!
Snap out of it, Finral!
Quit whining like you always do!
Asta's the one going face to face with a monster!
The pressure you're under is nothing compared to that!
Finral, how do your magic reserve look?
With so many spells I'm draining them pretty quickly!
I'm still managing though!
Guess it worked out that I spent the whole time here running away instead of fighting!
So I was right!
We aren't the ones who were slowing down!
Huh?
Not good!
He's starting to time his moves to our attacks!
There it is!
Asta!
Please, this!
This is nothing!
One blow just happened to graze me, that's all!
Now come on!
Let's go!
Hold up, kid!
Huh?
Captain Yami?
Fighting in close like you are, you should know better than anyone that blow didn't just happen to land!
He wants to learn your timing, your battle quirks, your weaknesses!
To do that, he's been holding back his attacks and going on the defensive instead!
What?
Really?
No!
If you fly in there hasty and unprepared, well...
Next time, you're dead for sure!
If you fly in there hasty and unprepared, next time you're dead for sure!
No!
Is that true?
Heh heh heh heh!
That's a dark swordsman for you!
With battle instincts like that, you're going to make an excellent main dish!
But what do you expect them to do with this information, knowing my strategy won't change their situation?
You pitiful humans!
Attack whenever you're ready, but the next one will be your last!
You don't know that, you overgrown furball!
Or you, Captain!
We can't know what'll happen until we actually try!
The hell I don't know!
I'm like a gajillion times stronger than you!
Is that right?
Then how about you quit watching and get down here already?
Oh, you went there, huh?
Hit me right where it hurts!
It's freaking killing me that I gotta just watch all this play out!
Do you have any idea how pissed off I am?
Kid!
Come down, okay?
I'm not telling you not to attack!
Huh?
What I'm saying is you can't do it like you did before!
You can beat him!
But you turn out to be smart about it!
Fear him!
Vanessa!
Kid!
Yes sir!
You ought to do it at a time like this!
Let me hear you say it!
Right here!
Right now!
We'll push further past our limits!
Okay, get ready!
We're gonna go even faster!
Got it!
Awesome!
Did they both hit?
We're still in!
Let me hear you say it!
Right here, right now!
We'll push further past our limits!
Okay, get ready!
We're gonna go even faster!
Got it!
Asa!
Did they both hit?
We're still in this!
Come on, you guys! Let's keep on pushing!
Understood!
Got it!
Kiddo, when I see you fighting so hard,
even though you have no magic of your own,
I start to feel a kind of courage I never thought I had.
I'd forgotten.
Buried the knowledge as deep as it would go.
Blotted out the memory of my weakness in the forest of witches.
Hey, did you know?
There's a big town outside this forest,
and I've heard there are tons of people living there who aren't witches.
Silly Vanessa!
You must have told us about that place a thousand times now.
Isn't that where all the other witches have gone?
To have fun and find boyfriends and stuff like that?
Why not escape this cage and join them?
You want to, right?
What?
No, that's impossible.
I mean...
I could never defy the queen of witches.
Hey, it's all right. Don't look so sad.
I know.
Want me to ask the queen of witches for you?
That won't work.
You're nothing more than a doll I made using my magic.
So if I can't do something, you certainly can't either.
That's right.
And this whole conversation is just you talking to yourself.
Someday, it would be nice to have real friends to talk to.
Yes, it would.
But it'll never happen.
I'm stuck here.
Inside this cage forever.
I'll never be free.
I assumed those were the cards fate had dealt me.
It seemed hopeless, so I gave up.
But...
One day I realized being stuck there wasn't my fate after all.
I'd simply lacked the courage to change.
I left the Forest of Witches and chose life with the Black Bulls instead.
And it was the right choice.
We hold the threads of fate in our own hands.
And it's our choice what to do with them.
Asuka! I'll pull you back in!
Just trust me and go!
DITRINESSA, I'M COUNTING ON YOU!
You ridiculous little fool!
Take it easy, you two.
We don't want to go faster than we can handle.
This is the problem with passionate people.
Much safer to be motivationally challenged like me.
Fenril.
Why are you wielding your magic so ineffectually?
For generations, House Vod has used offensive spatial magic.
And it has served us well as magic knights.
What use would that spell be in battle?
But...
I don't want to hurt anybody or get hurt.
That sounds scary.
Gutless weakling.
My, just look at how much of that column you shaved off.
You're amazing, Lungris.
An absolute genius.
Don't worry.
We'll have someone fix whatever you've broken.
You just keep practicing.
We'll take care of everything, dear.
Honestly, Fenril.
Aren't you ashamed to be shown up by your younger brother?
You're brothers.
How could there be such a difference in your abilities?
Why, just look at Lungris.
He's already been made vice-captain of the Golden Dawn.
And what have you accomplished?
You're nothing but a pack mule for the Black Bulls.
The worst magic knight squad there is.
Lungris will be taking over as head of House Vod.
I trust you don't object.
No, of course not.
I was just thinking it'd be a huge responsibility.
Take good care of the place, Lungris.
I don't need you to tell me how to handle my affairs.
You're a disgrace to our house.
Uh, yeah, I guess you're right.
But hey, at least the girls really like my pretty face.
I ran away from my father, my brother, my home, from reality.
Hello there.
You ladies sure are looking lovely.
Wanna go grab a drink?
I know a nice cafe not far from here.
I've got to say, darling, if you're as sweet as you are beautiful, I don't think we'll be ordering any dessert.
And then, I met you, Asta.
A boy utterly without magic.
Not too little.
None at all.
Instead of running from the fact that you couldn't cast a single spell, you faced it head-on and fought without ever giving up.
True, I can't hope to best my brother as I am now.
But, Yami?
What?
It's just that, why'd you let me join your squad, knowing I'm not much of a fighter?
Figured you'd come in handy as a chauffeur.
Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
I mean, it's not like my spells are good for taking down enemies or anything.
Maybe not, but you probably got your own way of fighting, don't you?
Huh?
There's a lot more to battle than just taking down enemies, you know.
Is it possible?
My own way of fighting?
I know I'll never be the strongest mage.
But I'll do what I can to make the Black Bulls the strongest squad.
I stepped away from my own fight.
And when I did, there were words I couldn't say anymore.
But I can say them now.
Asta!
I swear I won't mess this up!
Please, just trust me, okay?
Too late, Mineral!
I already trust you completely!
I'm impressed you aren't half bad.
But you'll be at your limit soon.
If even one of you slips up, you'll be dead.
And you'll take the other two with you.
How long do you think you can actually keep going?
Shut up!
You really don't get it!
We'll keep fighting like this for as long as we have to!
Asta said he trusts me completely.
And I guess it has to be true.
Because how else could we possibly be pulling off this ridiculous method of fighting?
Really?
How can you so easily put your life in our hands?
A drunken, lush, and a superficial slacker.
Still, whatever made you believe in us...
We won't betray your trust!
Well done.
Your ability to focus is commendable.
Although, how is your magic holding out?
You'll be scraping the bottom of the barrel soon.
Absolute amount of power.
That is the definitive difference between my kind and yours, you fragile little insects.
He may be full of himself, but unfortunately he's not wrong.
My portals are starting to shrink.
My threads?
They're screaming.
With my magic running out, they could snap any minute.
I trust you two and we're gonna win!
It's not just two.
Looks like we made it in time.
Oh yeah.
Ghost?
Charmy!
And...
That's grey.
And this might sound like a terrible joke, but that's actually what she looks like.
What?
Please, stop looking at me!
Save all that for later.
Right now, take this.
With all the magic power I can muster.
Mirror magic?
Reflect refrain!
What are you playing at?
You think with enough blasts one has to land?
I think you're right where I want you to be.
Now, Five Head.
Cotton creation magic!
Strike of a sleeping sheep!
Strike one!
Strike two!
You're out!
They want a smoke screen?
Good luck with that.
Ah!
Huh?
I've used my transformation magic to make some doubles.
I'm low on power though, so some of them aren't quite right.
Nicely done.
And you, keep going with that giant sheep till you run out of magic.
Aye aye, sir!
Ah!
I've had enough!
Time to plunge you insects into despair!
You're right!
Who has time to waste on despair?!
I've been crying for hours, baby!
I wish you were here!
For hours, lately, I've been crying for hours, baby
I wish you were here
Kimi ga kureta all those letters
Yumi kaesu tabi ni
The pain's gone
Hitori jamaai
Cause we are perfect as for
離れ離れでも
繋がる believe in you
いつも somebody
感じているから
Close side of me
And I'd love to follow you
Kimi ni go
You know you're not alone
Cause we are perfect as for
離れ離れでも
繋がる you and me
いつも somebody
Kimi ni
Watashi ga iru kara
Close side of me
And I'd love to follow you
Kimi ni go
kimi ni
Kimi ni
Clover Clips!
Three in one!
Right! I'll just pull on my thread and when I do, it will change your direction!
And after she does that, I'll use my spatial magic to send you somewhere else!
Put one slip-up and that's it! You're done for!
Are you sure you've got this?
Yeah, I'm good. All I have to do is charge.
Alright, Gordon. Let's do this!
Ready, set, green light!
We can win! I trust you two completely!
Come on!
Asta! We've got you!
As much as I like this game, Gordon, I think it would work a lot better if I could actually hear you when you said red light.
I'm sorry, Asta.
Your foe was just too terrible.
The hell we don't do you, you two.
Oh no, I insist that my friends are in trouble.
I wish I could go help them.
Please be alright, everyone.
I'm sending good thoughts your way.
Black Clover page 49. Beyond Limits.
My magic is becoming friends with anyone.